混乱之子 前情提要
Previously on Sons Of Anarchy...
我来处理
I've got this.
Juice.把工具包拿来
Juice. Get the kit.
我得知道.....那是你下的命令？
I've gotta know...that was your call?
不是
No.
我来这和你谈笔交易
I'm here to make you an offer.
我会把Gaalan O'Shay交给你 附赠一船的枪支 绝不拖泥带水
Gaalan O'Shay. I will deliver him with
a shipment of guns open and shut.
你想得到什么好处
What's in it for you?
豁免俱乐部一切关于枪支的指控 包括过去和现在的
Immunity, for the MC for all gun charges.
你必须重新审理一下Tara的案子
And you need to look at Tara's case again.
我需要那笔交易
I want your deal.
哦，我很遗憾，那个交易已经不存在了
Oh, I'm sorry, that deal's no longer on the table.
还有其他的事待定
There are other things pending.
既然你们退出了枪支生意 就应该我们接手
You're getting out of the
guns-- we should have that business.
这是我们的地盘
This is our territory.
这是我们应得的
We own it. We deserve it.
嗯 感觉真不错
Yeah. That feels good.
打在人身上效果更好
They work even better on flesh.
把枪放下 放下
Put it down! Down!
可没办法让林相信 这不是我们设计好的
There is no way Lin's gonna believe we didn't plan this.
我们把中国佬惹火了 奥克兰州那边就会有麻烦了
We burn the Chinese, things are gonna jump off in Oakland.
那么我们将失去江湖平衡
Then we lose the balance.
Clay的庭审时间被提前了
Clay's trial has been moved up.
他们明天就会把他转送出去，我们需要帮手
They'll transport him tomorrow. Gonna need some help.
该死，这是Sierra-4-0
Shit! This is Sierra-4-0.
我们遭到袭击
We are under attack.
Bobby被击中了 情况不妙
Bobby's been shot.It's bad.
干得好 Jackson
Good job, Jackson.
我猜 呃 你们已经投过票了
I guess you, uh, had another vote I wasn't privy to.
是的，确实如此
Yeah, we did.
这次是全体通过的
This time it was unanimous.
天杀的你们到底干了什么？
What the hell did you do?
我们干掉了杀害你们的人的家伙
We killed the man that killed your men.
这就是你要告诉爱尔兰之王们的故事
That's what you're gonna tell the Kings.
是你把他们都干掉了？
Did you murder them all?
我告诉你 你所需要的真实情况 只有这样的说法 才能让我们脱身
I am giving you the truth you need--
the only story that protects both of us.
那些待定的方案 现在已经取消了
Those other complications I had pending are
这就是说 我决定接受与你的交易
now off the table, which means I've
decided to take you up on your offer.
你与我们合作对付帮会 作为交换
In exchange for your cooperation against the MC, you'll get
你将会在Pamela Toric的谋杀案中得到豁免
immunity from Pamela Toric's murder.
如果我从一个帮会成员体内 取出一颗今天劫持事件中的子弹
If I pulled a bullet out of a
club member from today's shooting...
那算是证据吗？
Would that be proof?
加上你的证词 那就是了
With your testimony, yes.
你只有这一次机会了 医生
You only have one chance at this, Doctor.
损失了一个你的人 我很遗憾
I'm sorry you lost a man.
任何意外 都是在对付IRA时的连带损失
Anything that gets in the way of the cause
is just collateral damage to the IRA.
别侮辱我的智商 你要对付的可不仅是IRA
Don't insult me.That wasn't just the IRA.
你对Clay转运的事情一清二楚
You knew all about Clay Morrow's transport.
那就是为什么会发生野蛮的袭击事件--都是为了分散我的人力
That's what that wild gun chase was
all about-- to divert my manpower.
要是不这么做 死的人会更多
And without that diversion, you'd
have had a lot more dead sheriffs.
你指望我相信你的鬼话:
You expect me to believe that your lies and
你的这些诡计 都是为了保护我的人？
bullshit maneuvering was to protect my people?
随便你怎么想吧
Believe what you want.
我已经竭尽全力办成这件事
I did everything I could to make this work.
嗯 很明显 不是每个人都有好处
Well, clearly, it didn't work for everyone.
Morrow 和 O'Shay怎么回事？
What happened to Morrow and O'Shay?
冒了这么大的风险 就是为了自相残杀？
Why take such a huge risk just to kill each other?
Morrow 和 O'Shay打过20年的交道
Clay and Gaalan got 20 years of history together.
他们之间有很多交易 明里的或暗里背着IRA的
A lot of deals, both on and off the IRA table.
现在 我猜 不管他们之间什么交易 总之是谈崩了
Now, my guess is, whatever
deal they had set up went bad.
肯定会有妥协的办法
There's a lot of that going around.
我明白 这不是你理想的结果 但我从新闻看到的是
I know it's not the way you wanted it,
but from what I've seen on the news,
我已经履行了我所有的承诺
I delivered everything I promised.
KG-9，IRA的军火供应商 本地军火贩子
KG-9's, IRA supplier, local gun dealer.
我已经完成我这一方的交易
I held up my half of the deal.
你确实是个聪明人 Teller先生
You're a very smart man, Mr. Teller.
我明白了 你是怎样爬到你现在的位置
I can see how you've risen to your rank.
不好意思 我是继位的
Unfortunately, I inherited it.
嗯 我们都有各自命数
Mm, we all have a destiny.
也许吧
Maybe.
我必须先做调查
We have to finish our investigation.
然后才能确定 你是否履行了你这一方的交易
Then I'll decide if you kept your end of the deal.
好吧
Yeah.
进展怎样？
How'd that go?
她知道她被耍了
She knows she got played.
她也知道 她达成所愿
She also knows she got what she needed.
我们得等着 看看结果如何
We got to wait and see how it lands.
是啊
Yeah.
我去把Connor找来 叫他把枪带到Wahawa保护区
Well, I got hold of Connor,
told him to take the guns to Wahewa.
行 你们准备好了吗？
Okay. You good?
是的
- Yeah.
一切就绪 头儿
- Ready, boss.
我们随时待命 活跃得如同 在他老妈身上遗留的精华
I'm all over it, like jizz on his mama.
嗨 我妈早死了
Hey, my mama's dead, man.
那也不能阻止他
That won't stop him.
走吧 纹身佬
Let's go, Tattoo.
去你的 老大
Blow me, boss.
哦 谢谢
Oh. Thank you.
还需要点别的吗？
- Need anything else?
不用 没事
- No, I'm fine.
好吧 有什么需要尽管告诉我
- All right, let me know.
好的
- Okay.
喂
Hello?
早上好 医生
Good morning, Doctor.
呃 早上好
Uh, good morning.
我已经安排了跟ATF开会
I've been able to arrange a meeting with the ATF.
他们会安排证人保护计划
They'll be able to facilitate federal witness security.
我们将通过RICO法案来办这个案
We'll process through RICO.
我们将提供你和你家人的一切所需
We can give you everything you and your family need.
好的
Okay.
我该怎样做？
How?
你必须来我的办公室 带上那个证据
You'll need to come to my office, with the evidence.
我去不了
- I can't do that.
为什么？
- Why?
我被人跟着
I have escorts.
到你的医院办公室怎样？
Your hospital office,can you make that work?
我想可以
I think so.
你现在在哪？
Where are you now?
呃 大概一个小时的路程 我...
Um, I'm about an hour away.I...
快到了我给你电话
I'll call you when I'm close.
那颗弹头还在吗？
Do you have the bullet?
在 呃 我得挂了
Yes. Um, I have to go.
嗨
- Hey.
嗨 感觉怎样？
- Hi. How are you feeling?
我看上去怎样？
How do I look?
看上去被干倒了
Like you been shot.
多谢 大夫
Thanks, Doc.
请进
Come on in.
早上好
- Morning.
你帮我弄一下
- Would you get those?
哦 好的
Oh, yeah, sure.
很烫哦
It's hot.
多谢你提醒
Thanks.
好了 宝贝
Here you go, baby.
你的那位 拉丁情人上哪了？
Where's your Latin lover?
和婊子们在一起
With the whores.
真的？
- Really?
哦 老天
- Oh, Christ.
别紧张
Relax.
嗨 宝贝 吃点炒蛋吧
Hey, babe, ready for some scrambled eggs?
Abel?
嗨 你还好吧 小家伙
Hey, you okay, buddy?
妈咪哪去了？
Where's Mommy?
你和他们谈过了吗？
Who'd you talk to?
我给Roarke说了 他没说什么
I spoke to Roarke. He didn't say much.
BBC的新闻报道这个新闻
The BBC have picked up on the story.
我把细节告诉了他
I gave him the details on how it went down.
August那边进展怎样？
And what about August?
我们还没工夫处理这事
We didn't have time to get into it.
他们还有些烂摊子要收拾
They had some duck-and-cover work to do.
好吧 等你们要谈的时候告诉我
Okay, well, let me know when you talk.
嗯 希望尽快
Aye. Hopefully soon.
我想 你这里已经加强了保护？
Think you got enough protection around here?
呃 我们有Hugh 和 Malloy 看着
Uh, got Hugh and Malloy.
怎么了？你们真的认为华人帮会来搞事？
Why? You really think the Chinese
will try and hit us here?
Lin要是知道Gaalan被干掉了 他可能会有所行动
Lin finds out Gaalan was
killed, he might make a move.
你把那批枪放在Wahawa保护区会很安全
Your guns will be safe at Wahewa.
我们能在附近的谷仓里 监视附近的所有情况
We can see everything coming and going at the barn.
好的
All right.
回见 Conn
Later, Conn.
嗯
Aye.
嗨 哥们
- Hey, man.
嗨 兄弟
- Hey, brother.
Jax要我们过来看看 枪支是否安全到达
Jax wanted us to come by to make
sure the guns got here safe, right?
嗯 一切都万无一失
Aye. Everything....safe and sound.
嗯
- Yeah.
所有都在这吗？
- That all of them?
除了KG-9 其他都在这了
- Everything but the KG-9's.
很好
- Cool.
谢谢 先生们
Thank you, gentlemen.
不是吧
Really?
抱歉了
- Sorry about that.
不
- No.
别沾到头发上
Not the hair, man.
Not the hair.
千万别
Come on.
孤独地骑行在这尘世
Riding through this world all alone
上帝将灵魂带走
God takes your soul
徒剩躯壳
You're on your own
如乌鸦掠过天际
The crow flies straight
直飞远方
a perfect line
缠绵在恶魔之床
on the devil's bed
直至死亡
until you die
才将这一世轨迹
Gotta look this life
看个端详
in the eye
混乱之子 第六季 第十二集
英文字幕：n17t01 翻译：Dena 校对：Wilsonyy
估计你看过了关于Gaalan的新闻
I'm assuming you saw the news
about what happened to Gaalan?
我看过了
I did.
你干的？
Was that you?
我也爱莫能助
Couldn't be helped.
很不幸
Unfortunate.
我的人在车里吗？
Is my guy in the van?
打开
那批枪 还有Gaalan的手下在哪？
Where are the guns, and Gaalan's men?
这也爱莫能助
This couldn't be helped, either.
你明白“复仇”是怎么回事吗？
Do you understand how vengeance works?
亲自动手才能解恨
The satisfaction comes from the doing.
他们杀了我的人
They killed one of my men.
差点杀了我的侄子
Almost killed my nephew.
这些必须由我来解决
I need to do something to make it right!
我们为你拿到了枪
We got you the guns.
Gaalan也死了 爱尔兰人元气大伤
With Gaalan dead, the Irish are hurt.
他妈的      我不需要他们伤元气
I don't want them hurt.
我要灭了他们
I want them gone!
Gaalan的副手是谁？
Gaalan's number two-- who is he?
Connor.
问他干嘛？
What about him?
把他交给我...然后 我再把你们的人放了
Deliver him... and then I'll let your man go free.
这可办不到
I can't do that.
这样的话...我也不能让你的人活着
Then... I cannot let your man live.
开战对我们都没好处
Starting a war drains both sides.
战争不是我挑起的 我是被迫参与
I am not starting it, I am joining it.
我们走    快点
去联络Marks
Let's reach out to Marks.
老天
Jesus.
我们还没开门
We're not open yet.
Lyla.
没事
He's all right.
可以谈谈吗？
Can we talk?
进来吧
In here.
把那些杂物拿掉 坐吧
Move some of that shit, have a seat.
怎么回事？
What's going on?
我得给你吐吐槽 老哥
I got to lay it out for you, hermano.
我忍了好久了
It's been coming for a while.
好吧 我听着
All right, I'm listening.
我们Byzlats帮会---恐怕要完蛋了
The Byzlats-- I'm afraid we're about done.
完蛋？
Done?
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
我是说 发生校园枪击案以后
Look, when that shit
你把Renaldo的头轰掉了...那太让人抓狂了
went down with you and Renaldo, you
blowing him away... that was crazy.
但是 也没问题 好吧 我们的老大重出江湖了
But I was, like, okay, it's all
right, our OG is back in charge.
没错
Firme.
或许我们可以展示一些实力 开始招兵买马
Maybe we could show some weight, start recruiting.
嗨 我可没承诺要发展势力
Hey, nobody made no promises about growing.
这不是发展势力的问题
It ain't about growing anymore.
这是生存问题
It's about staying alive.
你把我们抛弃了 大哥
You bailed on us, jefe.
瞧 我知道你和摩托党合作经营Diosa
Look, I know you got Diosa with
the MC and you're all hooked up
还和Teller的老妈搞在了一起
with Teller's mom and shit, but
但是 我们还有自己的生意 老哥
we got business, too, ese,
你却不见影子....
- and you ain't been anywhere around...
嗨   嗨
- Hey, hey!
我才从莫须有的谋杀案中脱身
I just got rung out for a murder that I didn't do!
关于Arcadio那些破事
All that bullshit with Arcadio...esas pendejadas!
我还被地方检察官盯得紧紧的
I got heat from the DA.
好好瞧瞧 Fiasco 我感觉快窒息了 你看不出来？
Check it, Fiasco, 'cause I feel like
I'm drowning here, you see that?
我们都快窒息了
We're all drowning here!
就是从你和混乱之子打上交道开始
Ever since you met the Sons!
我明白我们需要同盟
Look, I know we need alliances,
但是这个飞车党...除了招惹麻烦 狗屁不是
but this club... they ain't been nothin' but problems.
大伙都是这样认为的
Crew feels the same way.
那要怎样？你要我一走了之？这就是你来这儿的目的？
So what, you want me to move off?
That's why you're here?
不   不   不   不
- No, no, no, no, no.
不是那么回事
It ain't like that, all right?
我们尊敬你 热爱你
Look, we got nada but respect and love for you.
真的 要是你离开我们 我们肯定会完蛋
Truth is, you step off, homes,
we are most definitely dead.
玛雅帮的Marcus Alvarez....他说要和你谈谈
Marcus Alvarez... he reached out, wants to talk to you.
他应该可以帮我们
Thinks he can help us.
兄弟 他怎么帮？
Dale!Help us how?
别这样
Come on.
我的意思是 我跟玛雅帮的人相处还好 但那只是....
I mean, I'm all good with the Mayans, but that's...
在奥克兰老家的交情
that's Oakland, homes.
就和他谈谈 听听他怎么说
Just talk to him, hear him out.
老乡帮老乡 这说得过去
The guys like the idea of brown helping brown.
要是你连坐下来谈谈都不愿意 大伙以为你根本不在乎了
You don't at least sit down with him, crew
reads that like you don't give a shit.
那我们就全完了
Then it's over, eh?
我也留不住他们了
I can't hold them together.
兄弟 好吧 你去安排吧
Orale.All right. Set it up.
兄弟
Orale.
嗨 宝贝
Hey, sweetie.
你在干嘛？
Whatcha making?
知道吗？Wayne在饭厅玩你的积木
You know, Wayne's out in the dining
room playing with your Legos.
我敢肯定 要是你去帮帮他 他可以建一个新房子
I'll bet he could use some help
building that new clubhouse.
他会和你聊天吗？
Does he talk to you at all?
不太聊
Not really.
他想他妈妈
He misses his mom.
来点绿茶
Green tea.
你饿了吗？
You hungry?
呃  不 谢谢
Uh-uh. No, thanks.
我什么也吃不下
I can't even keep anything down.
恶心比头痛更厉害
This nausea's worse than my headache.
好吧 明天中午再来看你
Well, we got to check you in by noon tomorrow.
要我给你的女朋友打个电话 让她给你带点什么？
You want me to call your girl, have her bring your stuff?
不再有什么女朋友了
There is no girl.
她 呃   回Frisco去了
She, uh... went back to 'Frisco.
回她前夫那儿
Back to her ex.
抱歉
Sorry.
要不我叫Wyne到你那拿点你用的东西？
Well, you want me to... send Wayne over
to your place, pick up whatever you need?
嗯 好的
Yeah. Sure.
好吧
Okay.
Gemma 我不太明白
Gemma. I don't get it.
我确实很感激你的帮助
I appreciate all this help.
我只是想知道
I just need to understand...
这是一种攻心战术吗？为了帮助你对付Tara？
is this all some kind of power
play-- helping me to hurt Tara?
Tara就要进监狱了
There's a pretty good chance...
that Tara's going to jail,
所以 她不需要我去对付她
so she don't need any more hurt.
但是 我确实需要一些帮助
But I'm gonna need some help.
我已经感觉到 我不再像以前那样 精力充沛了
It's been brought to my attention
I'm not as spry as I used to be.
所以 你需要我的帮助？
And you want me to help you?
嗯 我没精力再做一个保姆了..
Well, I can't afford a nanny...
所以 我没什么好选择
so my options are limited.
要不 是那位癌症叔叔Wayne
I got Uncle Cancer out there.
要不 是那些弱智的 身上满是精液味和Tig须后水味道的帮会女郎
I got some half-bright
croweaters reeking of cum and
还有 就是毒鬼老妈
Tig's aftershave... and I got the junkie mom.
喔
Wow.
我感觉我很特别
I feel special.
你背叛过我
You betrayed me.
但是 你又迷途知返了
But you bought it back.
并且付出了代价
And you paid the price.
我知道你很爱孩子
And I know how much you love that boy.
Jax永远不会让我接近Abel
Jax is never gonna let me near Abel.
我会说服Jax
I'll work on Jax.
你必须戒毒
You just get clean.
让自己回到正常轨道
Get yourself back on track.
还有 还是男人的那玩意好用
And go back to dick.
玩同性恋没意思
Girls are shit.
嗨 我还需要一些设备
Hey. I need some more supplies.
我得回圣托马斯医院去取
I have to head back to St. Thomas.
Rat陪你去
Rat will go with.
是啊 没他我可能就迷路了
I'd be lost without him.
需要我为Bobby做点什么？
Anything we need to do for Bobby?
让他别死就行
Don't let him die.
他没事的 走吧
He'll be okay. Let's go.
嗯        遵命 夫人
Mm. Yes, ma'am.
不是吧
Really?
这是医生的命令
Doctor's orders.
坐吧
Sit down.
我猜 一切都照计划实行了吧
So I guess it played out the way it was planned.
我指Clay的事情
Clay.
是的
Yeah.
除了Gemma和Tara意外出现
Other than Gemma and Tara being there.
注定会发生的 兄弟
Had to happen, brother.
为什么你改了主意 这次投了赞成票？
Why'd you change your mind, vote yes this time?
Clay罪有应得
Clay deserved the mayhem for what he did.
这一点我从没疑意
I never had any doubt about that.
但是第一次的时候...对于帮会来说 那不是最好的选择
But the first time... just wasn't best for the club.
对Jax也不利
It was no good for Jax.
但是这一次....就有道理了
But this time... it made sense.
是啊
Yeah.
真讨厌 得起来尿尿了
Hate when I gotta do this...
上一次你干那事是什么时候？
When was the last time you had your dick sucked?
我认为你现在干不了 兄弟
I don't think you're up to it, brother.
呃...去Diasa找找乐子吧 笨蛋
Uh... just... go to Diosa, shithead.
按个摩 找个妞 做做俯卧撑运动
Get a massage, drop a few oxy, get some head.
你需要放松放松 兄弟
You need to unwind, man.
你让大家都很紧张....特别是我
You're making everybody nervous...especially me.
我没事
I'll be fine.
这可不仅仅是建议
It ain't a suggestion.
去吧
Just go.
West!
我尿的时候 帮我扶着我那玩意
You're gonna need to hold my dick while I piss.
最好用两个手
You're gonna need two hands.
他是认真的吗？
Is he serious?
是啊
Yeah.
他那玩意很大 你得用双手
He's huge.You're gonna need both hands.
快来啊
Come on!
别磨蹭了
Ain't got all day.
把那凳子拿过来
Get the seat.
兄弟 见到你很高兴 Marcus
Orale.Good to see you, Marcus.
我也一样 Nero
You, too, Nero.
谢谢你抽出时间来见面
Thanks for making the time, huh.
嗨 不用客气
Hey, it's all good.
恕我直言 我很好奇
I gotta say, though, I'm a
little more than curious about
你说你们玛雅帮能帮我们yzlats帮
your offer to my boy Fiasco--
Mayans helping Byzlats.
那要怎样操作？
How's that work?
外地人在Oaktown搞的事
Shit that happens in Oaktown don't stay in Oaktown.
对大家都有影响
It affects everyone.
搞什么事？
What shit is that?
我们有微妙的江湖平衡---我们 九指帮 华人帮
We got a delicate balance-- us, Niners, Chinese,
还有意大利帮之间---我们都有各自的地盘
Italians-- we all got our piece
and we all got our boundaries...
我们都从飞车党那里拿货（枪支）
and we all get our guns from SAMCRO.
一样价格 一样品质
Same price, same quality.
从生意的角度来说
But the nature of the business,
飞车党掌控了一切 Jax在做主
MC became the de facto referee,and Jax embraced that.
但以后不再是了
- But not anymore.
那确实
- That's right.
你知道 他们退出产生的真空--不仅是枪支生意的真空 还有权利的真空
You see, Sons pulling out creates a
void-- not just in guns but in power.
据说Jax打算把爱尔兰人的枪支生意转交给August Marks
Word is Jax is handing over the
Irish guns to August Marks...
那给黑鬼们增加了很多实力 兄弟
and that move gives black a lot of weight, ese.
从而破坏了江湖平衡
Upsets the balance.
给我们每个人带来了大麻烦
Makes a real problem for all of us.
有道理
Cea mon
你们找找飞车党 把这事摆平
Have a meet with the MC, work it out.
Jax大开杀戒之前 应该考虑到这些
Jax should've thought about
that before he started killing people.
不是我要召集碰头会
Not my meeting to call.
如今 我不得不和华人帮坐下来谈谈 看看有什么对策
Now I gotta sit down with the Chinese
and see what my options are.
你为什么告诉我这些
Why you telling me all this?
你们有交情 兄弟
You got a relationship, ese.
生意伙伴 我和Teller只是生意上的伙伴而已
Business partner. I'm just Teller's business partner.
我们在一起经营一家小妓院 你知道吧？
We're moving a little pussy, you know?
他们飞车党的事 我可说不上话
I got no say in what he does with his club.
玛雅帮正在 Stockton建立分部
Mayans are starting up a charter up in Stockton.
我们有20个人 来自Vegas 和 Oakland 发展会很快
I've got 20 members from Vegas and Oakland gonna make the jump.
就如同在Oaktown一样
Things play out in Oaktown the
way I think, it's gonna be brown
拉丁人和亚裔联合对付黑鬼和白鬼
and yellow against black and white.
眼下 我知道Teller和你自己的事情有了龌龊
Now, I know that puts you at odds with
Teller and your own streets, ese.
老天  有必要走到那步田地吗？
Jesus Christ, that's the way this is gonna go down?
只是提醒一下你 兄弟 仅此而已
Just giving you a heads up, mano, that's all.
那我最好保持中立
Best we stay neutral.
得了吧 兄弟 江湖上可没有中立可讲
Come on, ese, there ain't no Switzerland in the hood.
我们走吧
Let's roll.
我们接到一个电话 一个为我们生产子弹的家伙打来的
We got a call from one of the guys who press our bullets.
他们在3英里外找到那辆卡车
Wahewa found the truck about three miles from the barn.
你的那批枪支不见了 你的人也挂了
Your guns were gone.Your guys were dead.
老天
Jesus Christ!
谁干的？
Who did it?
Lin 肯定是他
Lin. Had to be.
也许是从这里就开始跟踪卡车
Probably followed your truck from here, took 'em
等车离开大路 他们就下手了
out once they left the county road, man.
是啊
Yeah.
这一切都变得糟糕透顶
This is all going to shit!
这种事情是爱尔兰之王们最不愿听到的消息
This is the last thing the Kings will want to hear.
这就是为什么我们需要August Marks
This is why you need August Marks.
要是没有当地人的保护 你们的人就如同羊入虎口
Without local protection, you guys are
just drunk lambs at a wolf party.
Marks可以派3个团伙来这
Marks dictates to three crews out here.
其中一个九指帮 他们对华人帮可没好印象
One of which is the Niners, who
got no love for the Chinese.
和Marks谈谈
Talk to Marks.
至少你还有一个选择 可以呈报给Roarke
At least then you got an option to present to Roarke.
好吧
- Okay.
就是
- Yeah.
很好 我来安排
Good. I'll set it up.
你在这干嘛？
What are you doing here?
West告诉我 说你要过来取点东西
West told me that you were
coming by to pick up supplies.
估计我应该能这在“犯罪现场”碰到你
Figured I'd meet you at the scene of the crime.
哇哦
Wow.
你说 要死多少个“孩子”才能把这地毯弄这么脏
How many dead babies does it take to ruin a carpet?
你到底想干嘛 Gemma？
What do you want, Gemma?
Wendy需要一些抗呕吐的药
Wendy needs some antinausea scrips.
嗯...对于Wendy的遭遇我很遗憾 但是我没药房的钥匙
Mm... I'm sorry for Wendy, but I
don't have the keys to the pharmacy.
我可以去看看医生休息室找点样品药
I can check the doctors' lounge for samples.
要不然 只有到停尸间找点抗呕吐的药
Otherwise, just pick up some Emetrol from Mort's.
好吧 Bobby怎样了？
Okay. How's Bobby?
哦 他会好起来的
Oh, he's going to be fine.
但是我必须回来一趟
But I need to get back up there.
给我的律师取点资料
Need some files for my lawyer.
然后 顺便从医院偷点需要的东西
Then I need to casually steal from
the hospital I no longer work for.
20分钟后 我们大门口见
I'll meet you out front in 20 minutes.
遵命 夫人
Yes, ma'am.
Teller夫人
Mrs. Teller.
地方检察官大人
DA.
我忘了...
- I don't remember...
我叫Thyne Patterson
- Thyne Patterson.
哦 对了
Oh, yeah, right.
有急事？
Pressing business?
是的
Yes.
我们有3个警员在昨天的枪战中受伤了
We had three sheriffs injured
yesterday in a shoot-out.
死了一个
One killed.
也许你听说了
Maybe you heard about it.
是的 这种事情我经历太多了
Yeah, I'm familiar with some of that wreckage.
是吗
That's right.
对此深表同情
Sorry for your loss.
不 你才不会
No, you're not.
我对你也深表同情 这样我们就扯平了
But I'm not sorry for yours,
either, so I guess we're even.
一会我们在候诊室见
I'll meet you in the waiting area.
好的
All right.
你们的人为什么不去Stockon医疗中心？
Why aren't your guys
going to Stockton Med Center?
这里的眼科医生是全州最好的
The ocular trauma specialist
here is the best in the state.
哦 对啊 得要有双好眼睛去看清坏人
Oh, right. Got to have
them eyes to see the bad guys.
你说的对
Yes, you do.
Padilla先生还好吗
How is Mr. Padilla?
还是那样 利用他的关系网到处拉皮条吗？
Still spreading sunshine with
the power of human connection?
嗯 是的
Oh, yeah.
他脑子里只有爱
He's all about the love.
告诉他 我一直记着他
Tell him he's been on my mind.
我会的
I will.
祝你顺利
You have a good visit.
我要躲进小教堂里 去点上一根蜡烛
I'm going to just duck into
the chapel, light a candle.
也许你应该点上两根
Maybe you should light two.
Raymond Bowman 来自烟酒火器管理局
Raymond Bowman, ATF.
你好 医生
Doctor.
哦 我们应该等等她的律师
Oh, we should wait for her lawyer.
我...我没空给他电话
I... I-I didn't have time to call him.
呃 我们得快点
Um, and we have to hurry.
Gemma在楼下等我
Gemma's downstairs waiting for me.
她刚才来过
She's already been up here.
我们已经准备好了证人保护计划
We've prepared the WITSEC agreement.
包括了你的儿子
Included your sons.
由联邦法警负责实施保护
US Marshals will execute it.
免罪书将会由我的办公室签署
The immunity will come from my office.
把它交给我的律师
Send it to my lawyer.
你把证据带来了吗？
Do you have the evidence?
能看看吗？
- May I?
不行
- No.
一旦免罪书和保护协议弄好了 我就会给你
You get it once I know both the
immunity and protection are set.
这可不是玩过家家的游戏 Tara
This isn't a game, Tara.
我知道这不是什么该死的游戏
I know it's not a goddamn game.
这是我的人生 把文件交给我的律师 Glender
This is my life. Send the documents to Glender.
只要他说我受到了保护...今晚我就带孩子去找你
He says I'm protected... I'll pick
up my boys and meet you tonight.
这种作法不妥当 知道吗？
Well, that's not how this is done, okay?
我们会派人和你一起去接孩子...
We'll send an agent with you
to collect your boys...
不许别人去接我孩子
No one is collecting my sons.
我不希望 他们对父亲最后的印象
The last memory of their father
will not be of them being ripped
是被手绑着 枪指着
from his arms at gunpoint.
我会自己应付
I'll handle it.
要我合作 只能这样办
That's the only way you get my cooperation.
我们会把文件交给你的律师
We'll send the papers to your lawyer.
等他签字确认了 你把孩子和证据带上 来我办公室
When he signs off, you come to my
office with the boys and bullet.
这样行吗？
Can we make that work?
我们也没什么选择了
Not much of a choice.
什么时候？
What time?
一旦他说没问题 我会在6点之前到你那
He says I should take
it, I'll be there by 6:00.
我们到时候见
We'll see you then.
她还没有完全拿定主意
She hasn't made up her mind yet.
是啊 这是个重大的决定
Yeah, it's a big decision.
她爱Teller 她从小父亲就不在身边
She loves Teller, and she grew up without a father.
憎恨往往会恶性循环
Hates having to repeat that pattern.
要是她耍花样怎么办？
And what if she bails?
如果她不出庭作证 我会在法庭上让她完蛋
If she doesn't testify, I'll bury her in court.
如果她带着孩子跑了 帮会将追杀她
If she tries to run with those boys, the
MC will hunt her down and kill her.
是的 都安排妥了 他们都会在那
Yeah. It's all set up. They'll be there.
...我打发他去了Diosa
...so I sent him to Diosa.
他确实太压抑了
He's seriously twisted.
那小子需要放松放松
That boy needs to relax.
没事吧 医生？
- What's up, Doc?
嗨 医生
- Hey, Doc.
哦 真不错啊
Oh, that's good.
又是酒精又是大烟
Alcohol and opiates?
下次 我得带个心脏起搏器了
Next time, I'll bring the defibrillator.
哦 我喜欢这种刺激
- Oh, I love me some zap and tickle.
什么？
- The what?
嗯 是啊 你没试过在你的阴囊上装个电极吧
Oh, yeah, right, like you've
never had electrodes on your sack.
用直流电源？
- Direct current?
是的 你懂的
- Yeah, you know.
那是做什么用的？
What does it do?
Ay, yi, yi, yi, yi, yi!
Bobby看起来好多了
Bobby looks better.
他不应该喝酒
He shouldn't be drinking.
他知道
He knows.
这里完事了你会回家吗？
You headed home after this?
不
No.
我们跟爱尔兰人还有些事情要处理
We got some stuff to clean up with the Irish.
对我来说很重要
It's going to be a late one for me.
孩子们和Gemma在一起？
The boys staying with Gemma?
嗯
Yeah.
去道声晚安吧 如果你想的话
Go say good night if you want.
不 我还是待在这儿
No, I should just stay here again.
会更好些
It's easier.
好吧
Okay.
你的案子完了以后 我们得想想怎么办
After your trial, we're going to figure all this out.
对不起
I'm sorry.
嗨 我们该出发了
Hey, we should get going.
Tara打算待在这 你和我们一起去
Tara's going to stay here. You're with us.
我能去吗？拜托了
Can I go? Please?
我宁愿挨枪子 也不想帮他尿尿了
I'd rather get shot at than to
have to help him piss again.
哦 别这样 我们不是配合得很好吗
Oh, come on, man.We're so good together.
嗯 真爽
Mm, nice.
麻利一点 弟兄们
Make it count, boys.
呃 见鬼
Yeah, blow me.
谢谢你
Thank you.
再给我来一点
Want to get me more?
嗨
- Hey.
怎么了？
- What?
别再喝了 回到床上去
You need to stop drinking and get back into bed.
遵命 亲爱的
Yes, dear.
来吧
Come on.
帮我把他扶起来
Help me up with him.
嗨 亲爱的
Hey, honey.
有正事还是找乐子？
Business or pleasure?
多谢
Thanks.
找乐子 我想
Pleasure, I think.
你没事吧
You okay?
尽量吧
I'm working on it.
昨天的事我听说了
I heard about what went down yesterday.
很遗憾
I'm sorry.
嗯
Mm.
这一切本来不该发生的
It's not like it didn't have to happen.
或者不应该这样对他
Or he didn't have it coming to him.
一切都会好起来的
It'll be good again.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我有点失态了
I'm kind of high.
来吧
Come on.
把衣服脱了
Get undressed.
换上睡袍
Put on a robe.
我会叫个姑娘上来
I'll send someone back.
喜欢哪种类型的？
Preference?
温柔一点的
Someone nice.
好的
Okay.
哦 嗨 亲爱的
Oh, hey, darling.
他还没回来
He's not back yet.
还在Stockton
Still in Stockton?
估计是
Think so.
Clay的事情很遗憾
Look, sorry about Clay.
嗯
Yeah.
来一杯吧
Grab a drink.
我在帮Juice找个女伴
I'm getting Juice a date.
Juice来了？
Juice is here?
是啊
Yeah.
他有点...不对劲
He's a little... undone.
是的 确实
Yeah, I'm sure he is.
嗨 来了位伙计...
Hi. So, I got this guy...
太谢谢你了 亲爱的
Thank you so much, sweetheart.
别客气
You're welcome.
你必须躺在床上 好好休息
You need to stay in bed and get some rest.
没问题
Not a problem.
大伙都很爱你 医生
We love you, Doc.
他怎样？
How's he doing?
他睡了 我也要洗漱上床睡了
He's resting. I'm just
gonna wash up and do the same.
我快累坏了
I'm exhausted.
听上去不错
Sounds like a plan.
你和Roarke谈过吗？
Did you talk to Roarke?
嗯
Aye.
他的反应可不太爽
It wasn't a cheerful response.
但是他也清楚 我们没有太多选择
But he knows we have limited options.
他会和其他几个长老谈谈 会谈结束后给他电话
He's gonna talk to the other Kings,
wait for my call after the meeting.
好的
Okay.
这是Marks
This Marks?
这是大老板
That's the boss.
不 不 不
No, no, no. No!
你这混蛋 Teller
You piece of shit, Teller.
别担心 不会有事
Don't worry. It ends well.
爱尔兰之王们会把你钉在十字架上 小子
The Kings will crucify you, boy.
把你们所有的人都屠杀干净
Fierce slaughter on every one of you.
Connor先生 谢谢你的参与
Mr. Connor. Thank you for joining us.
你把我的人放了 我才把他交给你
You don't get him, until I get my guy.
Happy
你没事吧？
- You okay?
嗯
- Yeah.
走吧
Go on.
枪还在车里
Guns are still in the truck.
打开
爱死你们了 兄弟们
I love you guys.
我们也爱死你了
And we love you.
你还好吧
You're all right. Come here.
喂
Hello?
Knowles 医生 我是Thyne Patterson
Dr. Knowles.Thyne Patterson.
你和你的律师谈过了吗？
Have you spoken to your lawyer?
没有 怎么了？
No. Why?
他做了一些细微的修改 但是他同意我们给你的交易
He made a few tweaks, but
he likes the deal we made for you.
希望我们继续进行下去
Wants us to move ahead.
好的 我给他打个电话
Okay, I'll give him a call.
我们希望6点能见面
We'll expect to see you by 6:00.
好的
Okay.
我告诉过你没事的
- I told you it ends well.
要是那个老家伙一开始就给我脑袋来一枪?
What if the old man put a
bullet in my head at first sight?
那会怎么样？
- Then what?
那是你们的风格 不是他的
- That's your style, not his.
是的 因为他会把你带回他的仓库
Yeah, 'cause he would
take you back to his warehouse,
把你折磨一番 然后再割断你的喉咙
torture you for a while,
then he'd slit your throat.
这种行为太野蛮了
This is some real cowboy shit here.
这是必须的 要把华人帮打跑
It was necessary. Sets the Chinese back.
让你瞧瞧Marks展现的诚意
Lets you see what Marks can provide.
你听命于他？
And you answer to him?
Marks先生和Pope先生一样 都是我们的恩主
Mr. Marks, like Mr. Pope, is our benefactor.
他保护我们的利益
He protects our interests.
我们也为他提供保护
We protect his.
我们要等到天黑
We gonna wait till after dark.
把这个面包车停在Lin的餐馆门前
We gonna park the van in front of Lin's restaurant.
这就是发表一个声明
That'll make a statement.
幸会
- It was good meeting you.
是啊
- Aye.
再见
See you soon.
不 别再见
No, you won't.
得了吧 Teller
Come on, Teller.
别开玩笑
Who you kidding?
那么 奥克兰那边怎么办？
So, what does it do to Oakland?
不太清楚
It unravels a little.
我让Marks给你详细解释
I'll let Marks break it down for you.
他马上到
He's on his way.
好吧 好吧
Okay. Okay.
我不管这些小东西有多可爱 现在不是1896年那时候
Look, I don't care how
cute they are, this isn't 1896.
我们不做易货生意
We don't barter.
它们的毛皮很值钱
Their fur is very valuable.
我们可以把它们养大 然后做成毛皮大衣或者帽子
I figured we'd breed them, and make coats. Or hats!
软软的 毛茸茸的帽子
Little soft, furry hats.
我们只收现金和信用卡
We take cash or credit.
我们会失去这个好机会
We're missing an opportunity.
我会被毛球呛到的
I'm gonna choke one of little
fur balls out right in front of you.
真是无可奈何
I barely accept that.
抱歉
Sorry.
我这蹩脚的办公室主任 尽然想用维修费用和别人换几只金毛鼠
My crack office manager, wanting to trade repairs for chinchillas.
我觉得不太奇怪
Somehow that doesn't surprise me.
今天不太顺？
- Bad day?
一言难尽
- Complicating.
我帮会的破事
Shit with my crew.
想聊聊吗？
Want to talk about it?
请帮帮忙 Juice出事了
Help! Please! There's something wrong with Juice!
哦 老天
Oh, my God.
怎么回事？
What happened?
我在给他按摩 让他翻过身来
I was rubbing him down, asked him to flip over.
然后他就摊到地上了
Next thing I know he was on the floor.
老天 Juice Juice
Jesus! Juice! Juice?
嗨
Hey.
Juice 宝贝 醒醒
Juice, sweetheart!Come on!
Juice Juice 他的眼神呆滞
Juice, Juice.His eyes are pinned.
好吧 醒醒
- All right, come on.
让我们把他扶起来
- Let's get him up.
醒醒 宝贝
- Come on, baby, let's go.
他吃了什么？
- What did he take?!
和我在一起的时候 什么也没吃
Nothing with me.
他刚进来的时候 就已经很不正常了
He was pretty high when he came in.
好吧 查查看 垃圾桶
All right, check the trash.
来吧 Juice
Here. Juice?
嗨 兄弟 嗨
Hey, man, come on.Come on, man.
Juice
- Juice?
糟了
- Shit.
止痛片
Oxy.
哦 兄弟 你真是个笨蛋 那里有多少？
Aw, man, you idiot.How many?
如果是装满的话 应该有6片
If they were full, six.
让我看看 80多克 太糟了
Let me see.80s. That's bad.
醒醒
- Come on.
嗨 兄弟
- Hey, man.
要打急救电话吗？
- Should I call 911?
不
- No!
呃 是的 把那个给我
Uh, yeah, all right.Give me that.
我扶住他
- I'll hold them.
把那桶子递给我
- Give me the can.
好了 Juice
All right, Juicy.
醒醒 宝贝
Come on, doll.
听着 宝贝 要是你咬我 我就把你的舌头挖出来
Okay, baby, you bite me,
I'll rip your tongue out.
来吧
Come on, here we go!
真是多姿多彩的生活啊 老妈
Glamorous life, mama.
对了 宝贝 继续 继续
That's right, baby.Come on, come on.
很好 很好
There we go, there we go!
很抱歉 这一天的血腥味 先生们
Sorry for the bloody day, gentlemen.
发生这种事情让人惭愧
It's a shame this had to happen.
要干大事 从来就不容易
That kind of call, never easy.
但是 我要是被逼无奈 我很乐意再干一次
But one I'm willing to make if I got to.
我们都清楚了 你乐意和不乐意干的事情
We're well aware of what
you're willing and not willing to do.
是啊 其中一件他们愿意做的事 就是扩大你们的营销渠道
Yeah, well, one of the things they're
willing to do is double your network.
怎样才能做到？
How does that work?
我们在奥克兰市雷诺市 都有街头帮会的关系
I got ties to the street, Oakland to Reno.
往南一直到费雷斯诺
South to Fresno.
往北一直到俄勒冈州边界
North to the Oregon border.
很多重要的买家
Significant buyers.
如果你们能提供货源 我可以把销售额翻一番
If you can provide the product, I can
put them in twice as many hands.
并且他们不仅仅是街头帮会的关系
And it's not just street ties.
他贿赂了警察 法官 国会议员
He's got cops, judges,
council seats in his pocket.
Pope的企业帝国拥有全美第三大慈善机构
Pope Industries runs the third largest
charitable organization in the state.
这是我们的红十字地震救援包 是分发给低收入家庭
This is one of our Red Cross earthquake
kits we hand out to lower income families.
老天
Jesus.
当然 一般装的都是电池和饮用水
Of course most of them just got batteries and water.
这有多少?
How much...?
50万 我们的第一个订单
Half a million. For our first order.
把运货数量提高四倍
Four times the MC's usual shipment.
你告诉你们的组织
You talk to your organization.
和他们做生意 我是非常认真的
Let them know I'm very serious
about being in business with them.
如果有帮助的话 我告诉你我妈婚前的名字是McDuffy
And if it helps, my mom's maiden name was McDuffy.
你就这样把钱丢给我？
You're just gonna leave me here with the cash?
合作伙伴就应该相互信任
Partners got to trust each other.
干得漂亮 McDuffy
Well done, McDuffy.
你也一样 伙计
You, too, man.
不管结果如何 你已经尽了义务
Whatever, uh, happens here,you've done your part.
Trager的事情一笔勾销
Trager's clear.
谢谢你
- Thank you.
嗯
- Yeah.
我会告诉你爱尔兰之王们的决定
I'll let you know what the Kings say.
好的 把我的钞票看紧点
All right, keep an eye on my money.
他吃了不少 也许只是想爽一爽
Him dropping that many,maybe it was about getting
但是 那家伙看上去并不想醒过来
high, but, uh, that sounds like a guy who
really didn't give a shit about waking up.
是啊 我知道
Yeah, I know.
帮个忙 先别告诉Jax 让我和Juice谈谈
Do me a favor, let me talk to Juice before
you or the girls say anything to Jax.
好的 好的
Yeah, yeah.
他快苏醒了
He's coming around.
好的 我马上过去
All right, I'll be right there.
好的
Okay.
喂
Yeah?
嗨 呃  我是Tara 我 我需要帮忙
Hi, uh, it's Tara.I-I need help.
Bobby又开始出血了 其他人都和Jax在一起
Bobby's bleeding again, and
all the guys are with Jax.
他们要和爱尔兰人处理什么事情
They had something with the Irish.
怎么了？Bobby不是很好吗？
What happened? Bobby was fine.
他喝了一天的酒 他的血液变得很稀
He's been drinking all
day, his blood's so thin, his
创口也裂开了 他 他现在一团糟
stitches opened up, he's-he's a mess.
我 我需要人帮忙
I-I need another pair of hands.
糟糕 好吧
Shit. Okay.
你需要我去取什么东西吗？
- You need me to bring anything?
不用
- No.
呃 有 孩子有人带吗？
Um, is-is... is there someone
who can stay with the boys?
他们不可以来这里
They can't come here.
我在Diosa这边 孩子们在我家和Wayne一起
Well, I'm at Diosa. They're at my house with Wayne.
好吧 快点 拜托了
Okay. Hurry, please!
嗯 我马上出发
Yep. I'm on my way.
来吧 喝点东西
Come on, gotta keep drinking.
没事吧？
- Everything okay?
不 当然有事
- No, of course not.
开始是这个小东西服药过量 然后是那个家伙又开始流血了
First the little one ODs, and now
the fat one is bleeding out.
我得去一趟小木屋
I gotta go back up to the cabin.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
这里有我们 去吧
- We got this. Go.
好的
- Okay.
再喝点
- Keep drinking.
听话 伙计
- Come on, man.
谢谢 爱你
Thank you. Love you.
爱你 老妈 去吧
Love you, mama. Go.
我们能对付
We're good.
好甜蜜啊
That's sweet.
是啊 甜蜜
Yeah. Sweet.
呃 我也许应该 呃...带他起来走动走动
Uh, we should probably, uh...get him walking around.
让血液循环起来
Blood moving and all.
嗯哼 好的
Uh-huh. Okay.
你要来一下 亲爱的
We need you out front, sweetheart.
我们都忙不过来了
We're filling up.
哦...
- Oh...
去吧 做你自己的事情 这儿我来
- Go do your thing. I got it.
好吧
Okay.
Juice 嗨 来吧
Juice. Hey, come on.
起来
Get up.
我们得走动走动 呃？ 站起来
We gotta walk around, huh? On your feet.
1  2  3 起
One, two, three... up.
Nero
- Nero...
嗯
- Yeah.
哦 该死...
- Oh, shit...
我们走走
- We're gonna walk.
对不起
- I'm sorry.
没事
- That's all right.
一会就好了 老兄
We gonna... we gonna get you well, homie.
我也不想这样
I didn't want to do it.
我知道 我知道 我们走走 呃？
I know, I know.Let's just walk, huh?
走...Jax说过 那就是我应该做的事
Walk...Jax said it was what I had to do.
争取机会...对不起
Earn my way... I'm sorry.
她那么漂亮....那么伤心...
- She was so pretty... so sad...
你说的是谁？
- Who was?
那个孩子的妈妈
The kid's mom.
我下手得干净利落
I did it fast.
那就是我想要的结果
That's what I want.
我就是那样想的
I want it that way.
Darvany?是你....杀了她？
Darvany? You... you killed her?
Jax命令你干的？
Jax put that on you?
是啊
Yeah.
对不起
I'm sorry.
真的对不起
I'm so sorry.
把这个放在顶上...
Put this one on top of there...
哦 我来开门
Oh. I'll get that.
嗨
- Hey.
嗨 Gemma在吗？
- Hey. Is Gemma here?
呃 没在
Uh, no.
呃 我估计他和那位皮条客在一起
Uh, I think she's with the pimp.
妈咪...
- Mommy...
嗨 我的宝贝
- Hi, my baby.
我来了 妈咪在这
I'm here. Mama's here.
来
Come on.
过来
再见 Wendy
Bye, Wendy.
唔 你要干嘛 Tara？
Whoa. What're you doing, Tara?
我们去吃晚餐
We're gonna go get some dinner.
好吧
All right.
不过 呃... 我得开车带你去
But, uh... I'll have to drive you.
我想和孩子们单独在一起
I want to spend some time alone with my boys.
我理解
I understand that.
你让开 Wayne
You need to move, Wayne.
不行
I can't.
你懂的
You know that.
Tara 你打算把他们带哪去？
Tara. Where you gonna take 'em?
我...Tara 老天
- I... Tara, Jesus...
天哪 Tara
- Jesus Christ, Tara!
闭嘴！
Shut up!
你告诉Gemma你是被逼无奈 只得让我走
You tell Gemma I pulled this on you
and you had to let me take them.
你也是没有选择的余地
You had no choice.
妈咪 我们去哪？
Mommy, we are leaving?
是啊 宝贝 我们...
Yeah, baby, we are.
你觉得你能跑多远 Tara？
How far you think you're gonna get, Tara?
我们会很安全
We'll be safe.
哦 糟糕
Oh, shit.
被保护
Protection?
被联邦政府保护?
Feds.
什么意思？Tara 你做了交易
What does that mean? Tara, did you make a deal?
让我们出去 Wayne
Let us out, Wayne.
用强的话 对他们不好
Doing it the other way is
only gonna be worse for them.
我们走 宝贝
Let's go, sweetheart.
Abel  Abel 我才是你真正的妈妈
Abel! Abel, I'm your real mother!
宝贝 我是你的妈咪
- Baby, I'm your mommy!
闭嘴
- Shut up!
宝贝 我爱你 宝贝
- Baby, I love you, baby!
闭嘴
- Shut up!
没事 宝贝 没事
It's okay, baby. It's okay.
喂
Hello.
嗯
Yeah?
混蛋
Shit!
好的 我告诉他
All right. I'll tell him.
嗯
Aye.
Roarke和其他长老谈过了
Roarke spoke to the others.
他们打算给Marks一个机会
The Kings are willing to give Mr. Marks a try.
我们要看看第一批货的销量如何
We'll see how the first shipment goes.
很高兴听到这个消息
I'm glad to hear that.
这一路以来 非常有戏剧性 Jackon
It's been an interesting road, Jackson.
你是那个 我真的不希望再打交道的家伙
One I'm really looking forward to getting off of.
我们彼此彼此 老兄
You and me both, brother.
保重
You take care.
先生们
Gentlemen.
Filip.
一路平安 Conn
Safe travels, Conn.
嗯
Aye.
我们走
Let's go.
哦 Jackie小子 你让爱尔兰的种族关系
Well, Jackie boy, you
just advanced race relations in
进步了50年
Ireland by 50 years.
还有50万美金
And half a million dollars.
怎么了 老妈？
What's happening, Mom?
Gemma打来了电话
Gemma called.
说她要和你还有Jax到他家里见面
Said she wants you to meet
her and Jax at his house.
听上去很紧急
Sounded urgent.
通常妈妈们不得不做一些很难很难的决定
Mommies have to make decisions
that are really, really hard.
目的是为了保护她们的孩子们
To protect their children.
有时候别人不喜欢这些决定 认为这是疯狂的事
And sometimes people don't like that,
and it makes them say crazy things.
这就是今晚发生的事
And that's what happened tonight.
我很抱歉 宝贝
I'm so sorry, baby.
你知道 不管我做什么 都是为了你和Thomas
You know, everything I do,
Abel, is for you and Thomas.
这是我的责任
That's my job.
我非常爱你们
I love you guys so much.
好的
Okay.
我们唱首歌好吗？
Should we sing some songs?
好吧
Okay.
你就是我的阳光
You are my sunshine
我唯一的阳光
my only sunshine
当天空乌云密布时 是你使我快乐......
You make me happy when skies are gray...
我们去哪 妈咪？
Where are we going, Mommy?
爸爸也会在吗？
Is Daddy gonna be there?
一直不接电话
Still no answer.
妈的
Shit.
好了 进来吧
Okay. Come on.
他们的东西都不见了
All their stuff's gone.
她把我的儿子带走了
She took my sons.
我在圣托玛斯医院见到过Patterson
I saw Patterson at St. Thomas.
她肯定做了笔交易
She must've made a deal.
我会让州警去找她
I'll have my sheriffs start looking for her.
到时通知我
Let me know.
Tara出卖了我们
Tara ratted.
她把孩子带走了
She took the boys.
原创翻译 倾情奉献
英文字幕：n17t01 翻译：Dena 校对：Wilsonyy